<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Los Gatos &#8211; Spectrum Eye Physicians</title>
	<atom:link href="/location-city/los-gatos/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 14:39:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Monterey Avenue</title>
		<link>/locations/monterey-avenue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/monterey-avenue/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians on Monterey Avenue, Your Trusted Los Gatos Ophthalmologists We know that finding a Los Gatos ophthalmologist&#160;that you can trust with one of your most important assets &#8211; your eyesight &#8211; is very important. Along with knowing that you have found that perfect eye care practice there are some other vital questions that... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/monterey-avenue/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/monterey-avenue/">Monterey Avenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Spectrum Eye Physicians on Monterey Avenue, Your Trusted Los Gatos Ophthalmologists</h2>



<p>We know that finding a Los Gatos ophthalmologist&nbsp;that you can trust with one of your most important assets &#8211; your eyesight &#8211; is very important. Along with knowing that you have found that perfect eye care practice there are some other vital questions that will help you make your choice. Does its office hours fit my crowded schedule? &nbsp;Is the practice office conveniently located? Will I find a&nbsp;full range of services there for all my eye care needs?&nbsp;Whatever your eye care needs, Spectrum Eye Physicians is now near you, right here in Los Gatos. We strive for the best that eye care can offer! We take the time to solve your problems and meet your visual needs.&nbsp;</p>



<h2>Comprehensive Eye Care from your Trusted Los Gatos Ophthalmologists</h2>



<p>Our trusted Los Gatos doctors, Dr. Engelman, M.D., Dr. Fishman, M.D., and Dr. Lee, O.D., use the latest eye care technologies to offer you state-of-the-art eye care and surgical procedures. We are your source for the treatment you need close to where you live and work. &nbsp;Here you can receive cataract, glaucoma, and diabetic screenings as well as comprehensive eye exams and contact lens fittings.</p>



<p>Our doctors work with children as young as 6 months old to&nbsp;ensure&nbsp;your child&#8217;s&nbsp;optical&nbsp;health and acuity. By detecting any problems early, we can prevent any limiting factors to your child&#8217;s learning and&nbsp;development process.&nbsp;</p>



<h2>Eye Care Services Provided</h2>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians in Los Gatos is committed to ensuring your comfort and satisfaction with every visit. Our office staff works hard to accommodate your busy schedule by offering appointment times that meet your needs. Our trained staff will work with you to help you navigate your vision insurance coverage and provide financial alternatives ensure you can have best vision care possible. Our common vision care services include ophthalmology services and treatments for:</p>



<ul><li>Comprehensive Eye exams</li><li>LASIK</li><li>Glaucoma</li><li>Dry Eye</li><li>Macular Degeneration</li><li>Diabetic Retinopathy</li><li>Oculoplastic procedures</li></ul>



<h3>Schedule an Appointment with Our Los Gatos Ophthalmologists</h3>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians in Los Gatos is conveniently located at 431 Monterey Ave #3.&nbsp; Located in the heart of Los Gatos, a convenient eye exam can be scheduled to fit your busy lifestyle.&nbsp;We invite you to make an appointment for an eye exam or any other vision services by calling us at&nbsp;(408) 354-9510.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/monterey-avenue/">Monterey Avenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oak Meadow Drive</title>
		<link>/locations/oak-meadow-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/oak-meadow-drive/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. is proud to serve the eye care needs of their Los Gatos patients from the Oak Meadow Drive location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective Oak Meadow Drive eye surgery and eye exams. Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. offer... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/oak-meadow-drive/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/oak-meadow-drive/">Oak Meadow Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. is proud to serve the eye care needs of their Los Gatos patients from the Oak Meadow Drive location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective Oak Meadow Drive eye surgery and eye exams. Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. offer the comprehensive eye care services that you have come to expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians. If you are in need of an eye exam or other vision care, the compassionate and professional staff at our Oak Meadow Drive office is here for you!</p>



<h2>Eye Care Services Provided at our Oak Meadow Drive Location</h2>



<h3>Conditions We Treat:</h3>



<ul><li>blepharitis (inflammation of the eyelids)</li><li>cataracts</li><li>complications with contact lens wear</li><li>corneal disease</li><li>diabetic exams</li><li>pink eye (infectious conjunctivitis)</li><li>macular degeneration</li><li>glaucoma</li><li>flashes &amp; floaters</li><li>eyelid cancers</li><li>dry eyes</li><li>tearing (epiphora)</li><li>retinal tear</li><li>retinal detachment (evaluation)</li><li>watery, itchy eyes (allergic conjunctivitis)</li><li>retinopathy</li></ul>



<p><strong>In addition to treating the conditions listed above, Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. also provides:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Annual eye exams</li><li>Emergency eye exams</li><li>Dilated eye exams</li><li>Refraction</li></ul>



<p><strong>Surgical Treatment Including:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Cataract surgery (including laser-assisted with the LenSx femotsecond laser) with the full spectrum of lens implants (e.g. monofocal, toric, ReSTOR(r) / Technis(r) multifocal)</li><li>Ocular surface surgeries (e.g. pterygium, conjunctival tumors)</li><li>Glaucoma treatment with medical and laser eye surgery (e.g. laser trabeculoplasty, iridotomy, iridoplasty)</li><li>Anterior chamber reconstruction, and IOL repositioning (e.g. iris-fixated and scleral-fixated IOL&#8217;s)</li></ul>



<h3>Eye Care for the Entire Family</h3>



<p>While many eye conditions, such as cataracts and glaucoma, develop in older patients, the team at Spectrum Eye Physicians believes that it is important to start regular eye exams at an early age. We offer comprehensive services to all members of your family including full child vision care services. When children receive regular and routine eye care, beginning at a young age, they are more likely to continue healthy eye care habits throughout their lives. Vision issues can also be a factor in how your child performs at school, with poor eyesight causing many academic problems when left untreated.</p>



<p>It is also important for adults to receive regular eye care especially as they near middle age and their retirement years. Conditions such as macular degeneration, glaucoma, and cataracts can be asymptomatic during their early stages. Regular vision care can detect these conditions when they start thus increasing the patient&#8217;s chances of protecting their vision.</p>



<h3><br>Schedule an Appointment with Spectrum Eye Physicians at Oak Meadow Drive</h3>



<p>If you are in need of comprehensive eye care in the Los Gatos area, please give our Oak Meadow Drive office a call today at (408) 354-4740. We are conveniently located at 212 Oak Meadow Drive&nbsp;Los Gatos. We look forward to serving the eye care needs of your entire family very soon!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/oak-meadow-drive/">Oak Meadow Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
