<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Santa Cruz &#8211; Spectrum Eye Physicians</title>
	<atom:link href="/location-city/santa-cruz/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 14:20:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Dominican Way</title>
		<link>/locations/dominican-way/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/dominican-way/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cataract Eye Surgery and More in Santa Cruz from a Dominican Way Eye Doctor Santa Cruz is sometimes called Surf City USA, a dispute the city has had with Huntington Beach for some time. Santa Cruz County, which includes Ben Lomond, Swanton, Brookdale, Boulder Creek, Big Basin Redwoods State Park, Scots Valley, Watsonville, Freedom, Amesti,... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/dominican-way/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/dominican-way/">Dominican Way</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2><strong>Cataract Eye Surgery and More in Santa Cruz from a Dominican Way Eye Doctor</strong></h2>



<p>Santa Cruz is sometimes called Surf City USA, a dispute the city has had with Huntington Beach for some time. Santa Cruz County, which includes Ben Lomond, Swanton, Brookdale, Boulder Creek, Big Basin Redwoods State Park, Scots Valley, Watsonville, Freedom, Amesti, and the Forest of Nisene Marks State Park has a zip code of 95006. Surrounding areas include Gilroy (zip code 95020) and Madrone (zip code 95037). It&#8217;s also home to Spectrum Eye Physicians on Dominican Way, a leading eye care provider.&nbsp;</p>



<h2><strong>Vision Services at our Dominican Way Location</strong></h2>



<p>Whether you need Santa Cruz eye surgery, eye exams, cataract eye surgery in Santa Cruz, oculoplastics, LASIK, or other optical care, we encourage you to come to our Spectrum Eye Physicians&nbsp;Dominican Way location. There, our eye doctors can assess your vision health. If something seems amiss, we can recommend glasses, contacts, medications, or surgical procedures to treat the condition.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Here is an overview of some of the services you can expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians.&nbsp;</p>



<h2><strong>Eye Exams&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>Your Santa Cruz eye doctor can catch many&nbsp;with routine eye exams, among them glaucoma, diabetic retinopathy, cataracts, and astigmatism. You should make it a point to see your eye doctor at least annually, and sometimes more often than that if you need cataract eye surgery in Santa Cruz as well as any other surgical procedures.&nbsp;</p>



<h2><strong>Oculoplastics</strong></h2>



<p>For facial bone, orbital bone, eyelid, or tear gland restructuring or repair, oculoplastics&nbsp;is the answer. This branch of Santa Cruz eye surgery is recommended for those with thyroid eye disease, orbital tumors, orbital trauma and other fractures, neuromodulators, facial nerve weakness, eyelid and eye socket reconstruction, and eyelid malposition.&nbsp;</p>



<h2><strong>LASIK</strong></h2>



<p>For those who want better vision without the need for&nbsp;contacts and eyeglasses, there&#8217;s LASIK. This laser eye surgery is quick, painless, and can be performed in a single&nbsp;eye or both. Millions of people have chosen LASIK to improve their vision.</p>



<h2><strong>Optical Care</strong></h2>



<p>If you do prefer contact lenses or frames, these are available as well. After your eye exam, you can sit down with your eye doctor and discuss your optical care options. We have many types of contacts as well as hundreds of eyeglasses frames to choose from.&nbsp;</p>



<h3><strong>Contact Information and Operating Hours</strong></h3>



<p>If you want to meet with our eye doctors to discuss your cataracts surgery and more, you can reach us by phone at 408-354-9510. Our address is Spectrum Eye Physicians on 1663 Dominican Way, Suite 212 in Santa Cruz. &nbsp;Our office hours are Monday through Friday, 8 a.m. to 5 p.m.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/dominican-way/">Dominican Way</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
