<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Doctors &#8211; Spectrum Eye Physicians</title>
	<atom:link href="/our-doctors/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 13:40:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Martin L. Fishman</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/martin-l-fishman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/eye-doctor-stockton/martin-l-fishman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Martin L. Fishman, M.D. was raised in California, and finished his pre-medical studies at the University of California, Berkeley, graduating cum laude in Medical Sciences. He graduated in the top 10% of his medical school class at the University of California, San Francisco Medical Center, and finished a medical internship at Harbor General Hospital in... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/martin-l-fishman/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/martin-l-fishman/">Martin L. Fishman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Martin L. Fishman, M.D. was raised in California, and finished his pre-medical studies at the University of California, Berkeley, graduating cum laude in Medical Sciences. He graduated in the top 10% of his medical school class at the University of California, San Francisco Medical Center, and finished a medical internship at Harbor General Hospital in Torrance, California, a major UCLA teaching hospital. Dr. Fishman completed a residency in ophthalmology at Washington University Medical Center in St. Louis, Missouri. He then spent two years at the National Institute of Health in Bethesda, Maryland, as a Clinical Fellow at the National Eye Institute, where he performed clinical and laboratory research.</p>



<p>Since beginning practice in Los Gatos in 1976, Dr. Fishman has served in a teaching position at Stanford University. He is now an Adjunct Clinical Professor of Ophthalmology there, Director of the Pathology Section of the Stanford Basic Science Course in Ophthalmology, and has been recognized as an Outstanding Clinical Faculty Teacher.</p>



<p>Dr. Fishman has also been active in leadership roles, and has served as Chief of the Medical Staff at Community Hospital of Los Gatos, President of the California Association of Ophthalmology, and is a Trustee of the California Medical Association. He has a Masters Degree in Public Administration in Health Care. He is married, has two grown children, and enjoys photography, exercise, and gardening.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/martin-l-fishman/">Martin L. Fishman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Robert S. Mastman</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/robert-s-mastman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/eye-doctor-stockton/robert-s-mastman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robert S. Mastman, M.D. was born in Buffalo, New York where he attended high school and later graduated from the State University of New York at Buffalo with a Bachelors Degree in Psychology. He is a graduate of the Autonomous University of Guadalajara, in Mexico where he earned his M.D. degree. After completing an internship... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/robert-s-mastman/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/robert-s-mastman/">Robert S. Mastman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Robert S. Mastman, M.D. was born in Buffalo, New York where he attended high school and later graduated from the State University of New York at Buffalo with a Bachelors Degree in Psychology. He is a graduate of the Autonomous University of Guadalajara, in Mexico where he earned his M.D. degree. After completing an internship in surgery at the Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center in New Hyde Park, New York, he returned to Buffalo where he completed a three year residency in Ophthalmology. During that time he served as Chief Resident at the Buffalo Children’s Hospital as well as the Buffalo Veteran’s Hospital. His training included extensive work in cataract surgery, ophthalmic plastic surgery and laser treatment of the eye.</p>



<p>Dr. Mastman entered practice in California in 1982 and earned Board Certification of the American Board of Ophthalmology the following year. Since that time he has performed thousands of eye surgeries including cataract, Eye Plastic Surgery, PRK and LASIK.</p>



<p>He is a member of the staff of the Good Samaritan Hospital, O’Connor Hospital, Los Gatos Community Hospital and maintains privileges at Stanford Hospital. He is a member of the California Medical Association, the Santa Clara County Medical Society and the American Academy of Ophthalmology.</p>



<p>His interests include active participation in raising his four children, photography, woodworking and tennis. He was a partner in building West Valley Surgery Center (an outpatient surgery center now located on Bascom Ave.) and is a partner in the Spectrum Eye Laser Center devoted to laser eye surgery.</p>



<p>Dr. Robert Mastman practices in the Samaritan Drive and DeAnza Blvd locations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/robert-s-mastman/">Robert S. Mastman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tarek El Sawy</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/tarek-el-sawy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/eye-doctor-stockton/tarek-el-sawy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tarek El-Sawy, M.D., PhD is a board-certified ophthalmologist with specialty focus on plastic surgery of the eyelids, eye socket, and tear duct system. He graduated with degrees in physics &#38; philosophy from the College of William &#38; Mary in Virginia. He earned his MD and PhD degrees from Case Western Reserve University in Ohio, where... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/tarek-el-sawy/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/tarek-el-sawy/">Tarek El Sawy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Tarek El-Sawy, M.D., PhD is a board-certified ophthalmologist with specialty focus on plastic surgery of the eyelids, eye socket, and tear duct system.</p>



<p>He graduated with degrees in physics &amp; philosophy from the College of William &amp; Mary in Virginia. He earned his MD and PhD degrees from Case Western Reserve University in Ohio, where he garnered Alpha Omega Alpha (AOA) honors, while his thesis research was published in leading immunology journals.</p>



<p>He was elected Chief Resident and awarded a Heed Fellowship during his ophthalmology residency at Columbia University in New York. He further completed sub-specialty fellowship training in ophthalmic plastic and reconstructive surgery at MD Anderson Cancer Center and Texas Oculoplastic Consultants, both in Texas.</p>



<p>He is an active member of the selective American Society of OphthalmicPlastic &amp; Reconstructive Surgery (ASOPRS) and certified by the American Board of Ophthalmology.</p>



<p>Dr. El-Sawy delights in mentoring students and trainees and joined the full-time faculty in the Department of Ophthalmology at Stanford University in 2012. He most enjoys his relationships with his patients—both adult and pediatric—and being able to improve their vision and quality of life.</p>



<p>Outside of his medical practice, Dr. El-Sawy enjoys spending time with his wife and two young sons.</p>



<p>Dr. Tarek El-Sawy practices in the Blossom Hill Drive, Samaritan Drive, Santa Cruz and DeAnza Blvd offices.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/tarek-el-sawy/">Tarek El Sawy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yohko Murakami</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/yohko-murakami/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/eye-doctor-stockton/yohko-murakami/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Yohko Murakami M.D. graduated with Honors from Stanford University with a Bachelors in Human Biology and a Masters in Psychology. She went onto obtain her medical degree from the Stanford University School of Medicine. She completed her ophthalmology residency at the University of Southern California/Doheny-Jules Stein Eye Institute in Los Angeles, California and then returned... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/yohko-murakami/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/yohko-murakami/">Yohko Murakami</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Yohko Murakami M.D. graduated with Honors from Stanford University with a Bachelors in Human Biology and a Masters in Psychology. She went onto obtain her medical degree from the Stanford University School of Medicine. She completed her ophthalmology residency at the University of Southern California/Doheny-Jules Stein Eye Institute in Los Angeles, California and then returned to the Bay Area for a fellowship in glaucoma at the University of California, San Francisco. She is an active member of the American Academy of Ophthalmology, the American Glaucoma Society, the Association for Research in Vision and Ophthalmology, and the California Medical Association.</p>



<p>Dr. Murakami specializes in glaucoma and cataract surgery. Originally born and raised in Tokyo, Japan, she is fluent in Japanese and proficient in Spanish. Her research focuses on the investigation of new surgical, medical, and laser approaches in the management of glaucoma in the United States and Japan. She is also actively involved in teaching and mentoring ophthalmology residents and medical students at Stanford University.</p>



<p>Outside of her medical practice, she enjoys spending time with her family, traveling, yoga, dancing, and kickboxing.</p>



<p>Dr. Yohko Murakami practices in the Samaritan Drive, DeAnza Boulevard, Blossom Hill Road, and Santa Cruz offices.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/yohko-murakami/">Yohko Murakami</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>James C. Liu</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/james-c-liu/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/eye-doctor-stockton/james-c-liu/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the early investigators in the use of the excimer laser, Dr. James Liu is a specialist in refractive surgery. Dr. Liu is on staff at Good Samaritan Hospital and El Camino Hospital. He is the Medical Director of Spectrum Eye Laser Center on Samaritan Drive in San Jose, California. James C. Liu, M.D.... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/james-c-liu/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/james-c-liu/">James C. Liu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the early investigators in the use of the excimer laser, Dr. James Liu is a specialist in refractive surgery. Dr. Liu is on staff at Good Samaritan Hospital and El Camino Hospital. He is the Medical Director of Spectrum Eye Laser Center on Samaritan Drive in San Jose, California.</p>



<p>James C. Liu, M.D. has been involved with the teaching and development of laser surgery since 1989. He has lectured and published a vast number of articles in the field of laser vision correction, and is one of the authors of the first major publication in the United States’ FDA trials. A recognized expert in corneal problems, Dr. Liu specializes in corneal diseases and transplantation.</p>



<p>Dr. Liu received his Bachelor of Arts degree in Biology and Chemistry from the University of Missouri with honors in both. He completed his Doctor of Medicine from the University of Missouri with honors and did his residency in ophthalmology at Louisiana State University Dr. Liu completed a fellowship in laser vision correction at Louisiana State University during which time the first patient in the United States was treated with the excimer laser.</p>



<p>Dr. Liu is a principal investigator for VISX Laser Company and has been selected to participate in the FDA-sponsored clinical trials for hyperopia, as well as hyperopia with astigmatism. He is a member of the American Medical Association, the American Academy of Ophthalmology and the California Medical Association.</p>



<p>Dr. James Liu practices in the Samaritan Drive and DeAnza Blvd locations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/james-c-liu/">James C. Liu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ryan Basham</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/ryan-basham/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/eye-doctor-stockton/ryan-basham/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Ryan Basham is proud to be practicing in the very same town in which he grew up. He attended Bellarmine College Preparatory for high school and finished his B.S. in Biology at Creighton University in Omaha. Dr. Ryan continued his medical school at Creighton where he met his wife (Dr. Elizabeth Basham). Moving to... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/ryan-basham/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/ryan-basham/">Ryan Basham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Dr. Ryan Basham is proud to be practicing in the very same town in which he grew up. He attended Bellarmine College Preparatory for high school and finished his B.S. in Biology at Creighton University in Omaha. Dr. Ryan continued his medical school at Creighton where he met his wife (Dr. Elizabeth Basham). Moving to the &#8220;windy city&#8221; of Chicago, Dr. Ryan completed a year of general surgery and three years of ophthalmology at Rush University Medical Center. Then upon returning to the Bay Area, he underwent further training through a combined fellowship in ophthalmic pathology at UCSF and Stanford. Dr. Ryan was eager to join his father, Dr. Arthur Basham, in his private practice of 35 years in Los Gatos. Joining Spectrum Eye Physicians in June 2019, Dr. Ryan Basham continues to provide the Los Gatos community with familiar, quality care. He enjoys spending his spare time with his family in Los Gatos and surfing in Santa Cruz.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/ryan-basham/">Ryan Basham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Christopher Engelman</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/christopher-engelman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/eye-doctor-stockton/christopher-engelman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Christopher Engelman M.D. graduated with High Distinction in general scholarship from U.C. Berkeley and was elected to the Alpha Omega Alpha medical honor society while attending Tufts University School of Medicine in Boston, Massachusetts. After graduation from medical school, he completed his ophthalmology residency training at Stanford University followed by a glaucoma fellowship at Devers... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/christopher-engelman/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/christopher-engelman/">Christopher Engelman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Christopher Engelman M.D. graduated with High Distinction in general scholarship from U.C. Berkeley and was elected to the Alpha Omega Alpha medical honor society while attending Tufts University School of Medicine in Boston, Massachusetts. After graduation from medical school, he completed his ophthalmology residency training at Stanford University followed by a glaucoma fellowship at Devers Eye Institute in Portland, Oregon. He is certified by the American Board of Ophthalmology and is an active member of the American Academy of Ophthalmology, the American Society of Cataract and Refractive Surgery, the American Glaucoma Society and the California Academy of Eye Physicians and Surgeons. He also serves as a delegate for the California Medical Association.</p>



<p>Dr. Engelman is actively involved with the investigation of new surgical approaches to the management of cataract and glaucoma, serving as a medical advisor for Atia Vision, Myra Medical and Lumenis.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Outside of his medical practice, he enjoys spending time with his family, backpacking and reading fiction.</p>



<p>Dr. Christopher Engelman practices at the Monterey Avenue office in Los Gatos as well as the Santa Cruz office.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/christopher-engelman/">Christopher Engelman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jeff Tsao</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/jeff-tsao/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 19:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=doctors&#038;p=923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/jeff-tsao/">Jeff Tsao</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/jeff-tsao/">Jeff Tsao</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anne Kato</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/anne-kato/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 19:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=doctors&#038;p=924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Anne Kato is a board-certified ophthalmologist, who has cared for patients in the Freedom and Hollister offices since 2016.&#160; She specializes in cataract surgery, and has experience utilizing advanced-technology lenses such as extended depth of focus and toric intraocular lenses to correct astigmatism.&#160; As a comprehensive ophthalmologist, her practice encompasses the diagnosis and treatment... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/anne-kato/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/anne-kato/">Anne Kato</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Dr. Anne Kato is a board-certified ophthalmologist, who has cared for patients in the Freedom and Hollister offices since 2016.&nbsp; She specializes in cataract surgery, and has experience utilizing advanced-technology lenses such as extended depth of focus and toric intraocular lenses to correct astigmatism.&nbsp; As a comprehensive ophthalmologist, her practice encompasses the diagnosis and treatment of most diseases and conditions that affect the eye, including dry eye, macular degeneration, diabetic retinopathy, refractive error, and eyelid lesions. &nbsp;</p>



<p>Dr. Kato is originally from Southeastern Pennsylvania.&nbsp; After studying Neuroscience as an undergraduate at the University of Pennsylvania and graduating Summa Cum Laude, she obtained her medical degree from Thomas Jefferson Medical College.&nbsp; She began residency training at UCLA-Harbor in Torrance, CA, for a transitional year, prior to completing the ophthalmology residency program at Brown University in Providence, RI.&nbsp; Dr. Kato is a member of the American Academy of Ophthalmology and the American Society of Cataract and Refractive Surgery.&nbsp; She is committed to providing compassionate, evidence-based care as a physician, with a strong emphasis on the physician-patient relationship.&nbsp; Dr. Kato and her husband have settled in Santa Cruz County with their two young children.&nbsp; Her personal interests include yoga, hiking, traveling, film, gardening, cooking, and spending time with her family.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/anne-kato/">Anne Kato</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leeanna Nguyen</title>
		<link>/our-doctors/leeanna-nguyen/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 00:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/eye-doctor-stockton/leeanna-nguyen/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A native of San Jose, Dr. Nguyen earned a Bachelor of Science degree in Biology from Sacramento State University in 2001. She received her Doctorate of Optometry from the New England College of Optometry in 2005, where she graduated with honors. Her clinical externships included the New England Eye Institute, Fresno VA Medical Center, Cedar... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/our-doctors/leeanna-nguyen/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/leeanna-nguyen/">Leeanna Nguyen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A native of San Jose, Dr. Nguyen earned a Bachelor of Science degree in Biology from Sacramento State University in 2001. She received her Doctorate of Optometry from the New England College of Optometry in 2005, where she graduated with honors. Her clinical externships included the New England Eye Institute, Fresno VA Medical Center, Cedar Sinai Hospital, and Spaulding Rehab Center – a Harvard affiliate, in which she trained in the diagnosis and treatment of traumatic brain injury and the eye.</p>



<p>Leeanna Nguyen, O.D. is board-certified by the National Board of Optometry in the treatment and management of ocular diseases- including glaucoma and therapeutic pharmaceutical agents. Her areas of specialty include primary eye care, pediatric optometry, and pre and post-operative care of surgical patients. She has extensive knowledge of contact lens fitting methods and techniques for a variety of uses and needs including astigmatism, multi-focals, post-surgical, post-trauma, corneal disease/irregularities, CRT, and high refractive error. She has experience working with various lens modalities including soft contact lenses, rigid gas permeables, and multifocal design, and hybrids.</p>



<p>Dr. Nguyen is fluent in both Vietnamese and English and has a basic knowledge of Spanish.</p>



<p>When Dr. Nguyen is not practicing optometry, she enjoys spending time with her husband and two sons. She also enjoys traveling and is an amateur photographer.</p>



<p>She is committed to exceeding your expectations by providing you with outstanding eye care and strives to continually learn the new advancements in the eye care field to become a better physician.</p>



<p>Dr. Nguyen practices at the Cupertino location.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/our-doctors/leeanna-nguyen/">Leeanna Nguyen</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
