<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cupertino &#8211; Spectrum Eye Physicians</title>
	<atom:link href="/location-city/cupertino/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 13:56:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>DeAnza Blvd</title>
		<link>/locations/deanza-blvd/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/deanza-blvd/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Visit our Cupertino Ophthalmologists on De Anza&#160;Boulevard James Liu, MD, Robert Mastman, MD, Tarek&#160;El-Sawy, MD, Yohko Murakami, MD, and Leeanna&#160;Nguyen, OD are dedicated to providing the eye care and vision needs of their Cupertino patients from the De Anza&#160;Boulevard location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. Just like all of the Spectrum Eye Physicians offices, the De... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/deanza-blvd/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/deanza-blvd/">DeAnza Blvd</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Visit our Cupertino Ophthalmologists on De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard</h2>



<p>James Liu, MD, Robert Mastman, MD, Tarek&nbsp;El-Sawy, MD, Yohko Murakami, MD, and Leeanna&nbsp;Nguyen, OD are dedicated to providing the eye care and vision needs of their Cupertino patients from the De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. Just like all of the Spectrum Eye Physicians offices, the De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard location has all of the necessary equipment to provide eye surgeries and eye exams in&nbsp;Cupertino.</p>



<p>Our physicians at our De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard location are dedicated to providing&nbsp;the comprehensive vision care that our patients expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians. If you require eye care in Cupertino, the professional staff at our De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard office is here to provide these services!</p>



<h2>The Eye Care Services Provided at our De Anza Boulevard Location</h2>



<p>The ophthalmologists at the De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard location of Spectrum Eye Physicians are fully dedicated to our patients and we provide the most advanced treatments and techniques to ensure&nbsp;lasting eye and vision care. Our trusted Cupertino ophthalmologists offer all of the following treatments for various eye conditions. If you need a consultation to review treatment for these conditions or any other eye ailments, please call our Cupertino&nbsp;vision care&nbsp;office.</p>



<ul><li>Blepharitis</li><li>Cataracts</li><li>Diabetic Retinopathy</li><li>Dry Eye</li><li>Glaucoma</li><li>LASIK</li><li>Macular Degeneration</li><li>Spectrum Eye Physicians also provide a full range of contact lenses and eyeglasses and all&nbsp;General Ophthalmology services.</li></ul>



<p>The ophthalmologists at Spectrum Eye Physicians &nbsp;also offer a number&nbsp;oculoplastic procedures including:</p>



<ul><li>Eyelid/eye socket reconstruction</li><li>Enucleation/ evisceration</li><li>Orbital trauma repair</li></ul>



<h2>Cupertino Eye Care for the Entire Family</h2>



<p>Many people erroneously believe that eye care is not necessary until an older age. There are many conditions, such as macular degeneration, glaucoma, and cataracts that do not develop until the later life stages, but undergoing regularly scheduled eye exams is important at every age. The entire team at&nbsp;Spectrum Eye Physicians believes that when proper eye care begins at a young age it becomes a healthy habit that lasts a lifetime. Our services are for the entire family no matter their age!&nbsp;</p>



<p>A yearly eye exam with our Cupertino ophthalmologists can help to detect conditions that are often asymptomatic in their early stages. With serious conditions like glaucoma, early detection is key in preventing or delaying loss of vision. For these reasons and more, we strongly recommend that all family members receive appropriate vision care throughout all life stages; and the doctors at Spectrum are dedicated to providing compassionate and effective care.</p>



<h3>Schedule an Appointment for a Comprehensive Exam with Our Ophthalmologist in Cupertino</h3>



<p>If you are in need of eye care in the greater Cupertino area, please give our De Anza Boulevard office a call today at&nbsp;(408) 253-3083. We are conveniently located at&nbsp;10300 South&nbsp;De Anza Boulevard. We look forward to serving your eye care&nbsp;needs&nbsp;very soon!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/deanza-blvd/">DeAnza Blvd</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
