<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>San Jose &#8211; Spectrum Eye Physicians</title>
	<atom:link href="/location-city/san-jose/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 14:41:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Blossom Hill Road</title>
		<link>/locations/blossom-hill-road/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/blossom-hill-road/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tarek El-Sawy, M.D., Yohko&#160;Murakami, M.D. and Sonya Park, OD are proud to serve the eye care needs of their San Jose patients from the Blossom Hill Road location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective San Jose eye surgery and eye exams. Drs.... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/blossom-hill-road/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/blossom-hill-road/">Blossom Hill Road</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Tarek El-Sawy, M.D., Yohko&nbsp;Murakami, M.D. and Sonya Park, OD are proud to serve the eye care needs of their San Jose patients from the Blossom Hill Road location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective San Jose eye surgery and eye exams. Drs. Murakami and Park offer the comprehensive eye care services that you have come to expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians. If you are in need of an eye exam or other vision care, the compassionate and professional staff at our Blossom Hill Road office is here for you!</p>



<h2>Eye Care Services Provided at our Blossom Hill Road Location</h2>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians believe in providing compassionate and comprehensive care to their patients, and the entire team at our Blossom Hill Road location are no different. In addition to providing regular eye exams and general surgery, our San Jose ophthalmologists also offer&nbsp;the following services for the treatment of all eye conditions and the symptoms that other illnesses such as diabetes can cause. Please schedule an appointment with our Blossom Hill Road location if you require treatment for any eye condition including the following:</p>



<ul><li>Blepharitis</li><li>Cataracts</li><li>Diabetic Retinopathy</li><li>Dry Eye</li><li>Glaucoma</li><li>LASIK</li><li>Macular Degeneration</li><li>We also provide a full range of contact lenses and eyeglasses and all&nbsp;General Ophthalmology services</li></ul>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians also offer oculoplastic procedures such as:</p>



<ul><li>Neuromodulators (Botox, Xeomin, etc)</li><li>Eye Socket Reconstruction</li><li>Eyelid Reconstruction</li></ul>



<h2>Eye Care for the Entire Family</h2>



<p>While many eye&nbsp;conditions, such as cataracts and glaucoma, develop in older patients, the team at Spectrum Eye Physicians believes that it is important to start regular eye exams at an early age. We offer comprehensive services to all members of your family including full child vision care services. When children receive regular and routine eye care, beginning at a young age, they are more likely to continue healthy eye care habits throughout their lives. Vision issues can also be a factor in how your child performs at school, with poor eyesight causing many academic problems when left untreated.</p>



<p>It is also important for adults to receive regular eyecare especially as they near middle age and their retirement years. Conditions such as macular degeneration, glaucoma, and cataracts can be asymptomatic during their early stages. Regular vision care can detect these conditions when they start thus increasing the patient&#8217;s chances of protecting their vision.</p>



<h3>Schedule an Appointment with Spectrum Eye Physicians in San Jose</h3>



<p>If you are in need of comprehensive eye care in the greater San Jose area, please give our Blossom Hill Road office a call today at&nbsp;(408) 227-7122. We are conveniently located at&nbsp;393 Blossom Hill Road, Suite 265 in San Jose. We look forward to serving the eye care&nbsp;needs of your entire family very soon!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/blossom-hill-road/">Blossom Hill Road</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Samaritan Drive</title>
		<link>/locations/samaritan-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/samaritan-drive/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Superior Eye Care by Qualified San Jose Eye Doctors Spectrum Eye Physicians&#160;provide&#160;superior eye care and the very best in a San Jose eye exam. At Spectrum Eye Physicians, your San Jose eye exam is conducted by well-trained and experienced&#160;eye doctors&#160;lead&#160;by excellent&#160;and compassionate doctors,&#160;Dr. James C. Liu,&#160;MD and&#160;Dr. Robert&#160;Mastman, MD. Meet Our Top San Jose Eye... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/samaritan-drive/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/samaritan-drive/">Samaritan Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2><strong>Superior Eye Care by Qualified San Jose Eye Doctors</strong></h2>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians&nbsp;provide&nbsp;superior eye care and the very best in a San Jose eye exam. At Spectrum Eye Physicians, your San Jose eye exam is conducted by well-trained and experienced&nbsp;eye doctors&nbsp;lead&nbsp;by excellent&nbsp;and compassionate doctors,&nbsp;Dr. James C. Liu,&nbsp;MD and&nbsp;Dr. Robert&nbsp;Mastman, MD.</p>



<h2><strong>Meet Our Top San Jose Eye Doctors at Spectrum Eye Physicians&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>Dr. James C. Liu earned his ophthalmology residency at LSU in New Orleans where he also completed a fellowship in laser vision corrective surgery. He mainly practices&nbsp;at our Samaritan Drive clinic where he&nbsp;is specialized in refractive surgery and is one of the early investigators of the use of the&nbsp;excimer&nbsp;laser for laser vision correction surgery. Dr. Liu also conducts&nbsp;eye surgery and is an expert in corneal problems, disease, and transplantation.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Dr. Robert&nbsp;Mastman, MD&nbsp;trained in Ophthalmology in Buffalo, New York and is a specialist in cataract, Ophthalmologic Plastic surgery, and corneal laser treatments. Dr.&nbsp;Mastman&nbsp;conducts eye surgery in our San Jose office and has performed thousands of&nbsp;eye surgeries&nbsp;including PPK (Photorefractive&nbsp;Keratectomy) and&nbsp;LASIK&nbsp;operations.</p>



<h2><strong>San Jose Eye Exam and Treatments of Eye Diseases&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>At Spectrum Eye Physicians our&nbsp;eye doctors&nbsp;perform a complete eye exam including a check of visual acuity, a slit lamp exam of the front of the eye, a dilated exam to examine the retina (back of the eye) and a refraction to determine if any corrective lenses are needed. Prescription eyeglasses and frames and contact lenses are available from the optical department which is staffed by licensed Doctor of Optometry. Eye diseases evaluated and treated include Glaucoma, Cataracts, Macular Degeneration, Dry Eyes, Pediatric Child Eye Health Exams, Ortho-K treatments and cosmetic eye surgery.</p>



<h3><strong>Contact Us Today</strong></h3>



<p>At our&nbsp;ophthalmology&nbsp;office,&nbsp;you will receive the very best in eye care by our San Jose eye doctors and the entire eye care team. Whether you need an eye exam or&nbsp;eye surgery for cataracts or a corneal disease, you can be assured of competent, compassionate treatment by experienced&nbsp;Board Certified San Jose eye doctors.&nbsp;</p>



<p>To make an appointment at&nbsp;Spectrum Eye Physicians – Samaritan Drive&nbsp;clinic, call&nbsp;(408) 358-2029 today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/samaritan-drive/">Samaritan Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Laser Center in San Jose</title>
		<link>/locations/laser-center-in-san-jose/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/laser-center-in-san-jose/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/laser-center-in-san-jose/">Laser Center in San Jose</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/laser-center-in-san-jose/">Laser Center in San Jose</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
