<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Locations &#8211; Spectrum Eye Physicians</title>
	<atom:link href="/locations/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 14:51:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Blossom Hill Road</title>
		<link>/locations/blossom-hill-road/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/blossom-hill-road/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tarek El-Sawy, M.D., Yohko&#160;Murakami, M.D. and Sonya Park, OD are proud to serve the eye care needs of their San Jose patients from the Blossom Hill Road location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective San Jose eye surgery and eye exams. Drs.... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/blossom-hill-road/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/blossom-hill-road/">Blossom Hill Road</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Tarek El-Sawy, M.D., Yohko&nbsp;Murakami, M.D. and Sonya Park, OD are proud to serve the eye care needs of their San Jose patients from the Blossom Hill Road location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective San Jose eye surgery and eye exams. Drs. Murakami and Park offer the comprehensive eye care services that you have come to expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians. If you are in need of an eye exam or other vision care, the compassionate and professional staff at our Blossom Hill Road office is here for you!</p>



<h2>Eye Care Services Provided at our Blossom Hill Road Location</h2>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians believe in providing compassionate and comprehensive care to their patients, and the entire team at our Blossom Hill Road location are no different. In addition to providing regular eye exams and general surgery, our San Jose ophthalmologists also offer&nbsp;the following services for the treatment of all eye conditions and the symptoms that other illnesses such as diabetes can cause. Please schedule an appointment with our Blossom Hill Road location if you require treatment for any eye condition including the following:</p>



<ul><li>Blepharitis</li><li>Cataracts</li><li>Diabetic Retinopathy</li><li>Dry Eye</li><li>Glaucoma</li><li>LASIK</li><li>Macular Degeneration</li><li>We also provide a full range of contact lenses and eyeglasses and all&nbsp;General Ophthalmology services</li></ul>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians also offer oculoplastic procedures such as:</p>



<ul><li>Neuromodulators (Botox, Xeomin, etc)</li><li>Eye Socket Reconstruction</li><li>Eyelid Reconstruction</li></ul>



<h2>Eye Care for the Entire Family</h2>



<p>While many eye&nbsp;conditions, such as cataracts and glaucoma, develop in older patients, the team at Spectrum Eye Physicians believes that it is important to start regular eye exams at an early age. We offer comprehensive services to all members of your family including full child vision care services. When children receive regular and routine eye care, beginning at a young age, they are more likely to continue healthy eye care habits throughout their lives. Vision issues can also be a factor in how your child performs at school, with poor eyesight causing many academic problems when left untreated.</p>



<p>It is also important for adults to receive regular eyecare especially as they near middle age and their retirement years. Conditions such as macular degeneration, glaucoma, and cataracts can be asymptomatic during their early stages. Regular vision care can detect these conditions when they start thus increasing the patient&#8217;s chances of protecting their vision.</p>



<h3>Schedule an Appointment with Spectrum Eye Physicians in San Jose</h3>



<p>If you are in need of comprehensive eye care in the greater San Jose area, please give our Blossom Hill Road office a call today at&nbsp;(408) 227-7122. We are conveniently located at&nbsp;393 Blossom Hill Road, Suite 265 in San Jose. We look forward to serving the eye care&nbsp;needs of your entire family very soon!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/blossom-hill-road/">Blossom Hill Road</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DeAnza Blvd</title>
		<link>/locations/deanza-blvd/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/deanza-blvd/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Visit our Cupertino Ophthalmologists on De Anza&#160;Boulevard James Liu, MD, Robert Mastman, MD, Tarek&#160;El-Sawy, MD, Yohko Murakami, MD, and Leeanna&#160;Nguyen, OD are dedicated to providing the eye care and vision needs of their Cupertino patients from the De Anza&#160;Boulevard location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. Just like all of the Spectrum Eye Physicians offices, the De... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/deanza-blvd/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/deanza-blvd/">DeAnza Blvd</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Visit our Cupertino Ophthalmologists on De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard</h2>



<p>James Liu, MD, Robert Mastman, MD, Tarek&nbsp;El-Sawy, MD, Yohko Murakami, MD, and Leeanna&nbsp;Nguyen, OD are dedicated to providing the eye care and vision needs of their Cupertino patients from the De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. Just like all of the Spectrum Eye Physicians offices, the De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard location has all of the necessary equipment to provide eye surgeries and eye exams in&nbsp;Cupertino.</p>



<p>Our physicians at our De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard location are dedicated to providing&nbsp;the comprehensive vision care that our patients expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians. If you require eye care in Cupertino, the professional staff at our De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard office is here to provide these services!</p>



<h2>The Eye Care Services Provided at our De Anza Boulevard Location</h2>



<p>The ophthalmologists at the De Anza&nbsp;Boulevard location of Spectrum Eye Physicians are fully dedicated to our patients and we provide the most advanced treatments and techniques to ensure&nbsp;lasting eye and vision care. Our trusted Cupertino ophthalmologists offer all of the following treatments for various eye conditions. If you need a consultation to review treatment for these conditions or any other eye ailments, please call our Cupertino&nbsp;vision care&nbsp;office.</p>



<ul><li>Blepharitis</li><li>Cataracts</li><li>Diabetic Retinopathy</li><li>Dry Eye</li><li>Glaucoma</li><li>LASIK</li><li>Macular Degeneration</li><li>Spectrum Eye Physicians also provide a full range of contact lenses and eyeglasses and all&nbsp;General Ophthalmology services.</li></ul>



<p>The ophthalmologists at Spectrum Eye Physicians &nbsp;also offer a number&nbsp;oculoplastic procedures including:</p>



<ul><li>Eyelid/eye socket reconstruction</li><li>Enucleation/ evisceration</li><li>Orbital trauma repair</li></ul>



<h2>Cupertino Eye Care for the Entire Family</h2>



<p>Many people erroneously believe that eye care is not necessary until an older age. There are many conditions, such as macular degeneration, glaucoma, and cataracts that do not develop until the later life stages, but undergoing regularly scheduled eye exams is important at every age. The entire team at&nbsp;Spectrum Eye Physicians believes that when proper eye care begins at a young age it becomes a healthy habit that lasts a lifetime. Our services are for the entire family no matter their age!&nbsp;</p>



<p>A yearly eye exam with our Cupertino ophthalmologists can help to detect conditions that are often asymptomatic in their early stages. With serious conditions like glaucoma, early detection is key in preventing or delaying loss of vision. For these reasons and more, we strongly recommend that all family members receive appropriate vision care throughout all life stages; and the doctors at Spectrum are dedicated to providing compassionate and effective care.</p>



<h3>Schedule an Appointment for a Comprehensive Exam with Our Ophthalmologist in Cupertino</h3>



<p>If you are in need of eye care in the greater Cupertino area, please give our De Anza Boulevard office a call today at&nbsp;(408) 253-3083. We are conveniently located at&nbsp;10300 South&nbsp;De Anza Boulevard. We look forward to serving your eye care&nbsp;needs&nbsp;very soon!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/deanza-blvd/">DeAnza Blvd</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dominican Way</title>
		<link>/locations/dominican-way/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/dominican-way/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cataract Eye Surgery and More in Santa Cruz from a Dominican Way Eye Doctor Santa Cruz is sometimes called Surf City USA, a dispute the city has had with Huntington Beach for some time. Santa Cruz County, which includes Ben Lomond, Swanton, Brookdale, Boulder Creek, Big Basin Redwoods State Park, Scots Valley, Watsonville, Freedom, Amesti,... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/dominican-way/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/dominican-way/">Dominican Way</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2><strong>Cataract Eye Surgery and More in Santa Cruz from a Dominican Way Eye Doctor</strong></h2>



<p>Santa Cruz is sometimes called Surf City USA, a dispute the city has had with Huntington Beach for some time. Santa Cruz County, which includes Ben Lomond, Swanton, Brookdale, Boulder Creek, Big Basin Redwoods State Park, Scots Valley, Watsonville, Freedom, Amesti, and the Forest of Nisene Marks State Park has a zip code of 95006. Surrounding areas include Gilroy (zip code 95020) and Madrone (zip code 95037). It&#8217;s also home to Spectrum Eye Physicians on Dominican Way, a leading eye care provider.&nbsp;</p>



<h2><strong>Vision Services at our Dominican Way Location</strong></h2>



<p>Whether you need Santa Cruz eye surgery, eye exams, cataract eye surgery in Santa Cruz, oculoplastics, LASIK, or other optical care, we encourage you to come to our Spectrum Eye Physicians&nbsp;Dominican Way location. There, our eye doctors can assess your vision health. If something seems amiss, we can recommend glasses, contacts, medications, or surgical procedures to treat the condition.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Here is an overview of some of the services you can expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians.&nbsp;</p>



<h2><strong>Eye Exams&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>Your Santa Cruz eye doctor can catch many&nbsp;with routine eye exams, among them glaucoma, diabetic retinopathy, cataracts, and astigmatism. You should make it a point to see your eye doctor at least annually, and sometimes more often than that if you need cataract eye surgery in Santa Cruz as well as any other surgical procedures.&nbsp;</p>



<h2><strong>Oculoplastics</strong></h2>



<p>For facial bone, orbital bone, eyelid, or tear gland restructuring or repair, oculoplastics&nbsp;is the answer. This branch of Santa Cruz eye surgery is recommended for those with thyroid eye disease, orbital tumors, orbital trauma and other fractures, neuromodulators, facial nerve weakness, eyelid and eye socket reconstruction, and eyelid malposition.&nbsp;</p>



<h2><strong>LASIK</strong></h2>



<p>For those who want better vision without the need for&nbsp;contacts and eyeglasses, there&#8217;s LASIK. This laser eye surgery is quick, painless, and can be performed in a single&nbsp;eye or both. Millions of people have chosen LASIK to improve their vision.</p>



<h2><strong>Optical Care</strong></h2>



<p>If you do prefer contact lenses or frames, these are available as well. After your eye exam, you can sit down with your eye doctor and discuss your optical care options. We have many types of contacts as well as hundreds of eyeglasses frames to choose from.&nbsp;</p>



<h3><strong>Contact Information and Operating Hours</strong></h3>



<p>If you want to meet with our eye doctors to discuss your cataracts surgery and more, you can reach us by phone at 408-354-9510. Our address is Spectrum Eye Physicians on 1663 Dominican Way, Suite 212 in Santa Cruz. &nbsp;Our office hours are Monday through Friday, 8 a.m. to 5 p.m.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/dominican-way/">Dominican Way</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monterey Avenue</title>
		<link>/locations/monterey-avenue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/monterey-avenue/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians on Monterey Avenue, Your Trusted Los Gatos Ophthalmologists We know that finding a Los Gatos ophthalmologist&#160;that you can trust with one of your most important assets &#8211; your eyesight &#8211; is very important. Along with knowing that you have found that perfect eye care practice there are some other vital questions that... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/monterey-avenue/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/monterey-avenue/">Monterey Avenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>Spectrum Eye Physicians on Monterey Avenue, Your Trusted Los Gatos Ophthalmologists</h2>



<p>We know that finding a Los Gatos ophthalmologist&nbsp;that you can trust with one of your most important assets &#8211; your eyesight &#8211; is very important. Along with knowing that you have found that perfect eye care practice there are some other vital questions that will help you make your choice. Does its office hours fit my crowded schedule? &nbsp;Is the practice office conveniently located? Will I find a&nbsp;full range of services there for all my eye care needs?&nbsp;Whatever your eye care needs, Spectrum Eye Physicians is now near you, right here in Los Gatos. We strive for the best that eye care can offer! We take the time to solve your problems and meet your visual needs.&nbsp;</p>



<h2>Comprehensive Eye Care from your Trusted Los Gatos Ophthalmologists</h2>



<p>Our trusted Los Gatos doctors, Dr. Engelman, M.D., Dr. Fishman, M.D., and Dr. Lee, O.D., use the latest eye care technologies to offer you state-of-the-art eye care and surgical procedures. We are your source for the treatment you need close to where you live and work. &nbsp;Here you can receive cataract, glaucoma, and diabetic screenings as well as comprehensive eye exams and contact lens fittings.</p>



<p>Our doctors work with children as young as 6 months old to&nbsp;ensure&nbsp;your child&#8217;s&nbsp;optical&nbsp;health and acuity. By detecting any problems early, we can prevent any limiting factors to your child&#8217;s learning and&nbsp;development process.&nbsp;</p>



<h2>Eye Care Services Provided</h2>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians in Los Gatos is committed to ensuring your comfort and satisfaction with every visit. Our office staff works hard to accommodate your busy schedule by offering appointment times that meet your needs. Our trained staff will work with you to help you navigate your vision insurance coverage and provide financial alternatives ensure you can have best vision care possible. Our common vision care services include ophthalmology services and treatments for:</p>



<ul><li>Comprehensive Eye exams</li><li>LASIK</li><li>Glaucoma</li><li>Dry Eye</li><li>Macular Degeneration</li><li>Diabetic Retinopathy</li><li>Oculoplastic procedures</li></ul>



<h3>Schedule an Appointment with Our Los Gatos Ophthalmologists</h3>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians in Los Gatos is conveniently located at 431 Monterey Ave #3.&nbsp; Located in the heart of Los Gatos, a convenient eye exam can be scheduled to fit your busy lifestyle.&nbsp;We invite you to make an appointment for an eye exam or any other vision services by calling us at&nbsp;(408) 354-9510.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/monterey-avenue/">Monterey Avenue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oak Meadow Drive</title>
		<link>/locations/oak-meadow-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/oak-meadow-drive/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. is proud to serve the eye care needs of their Los Gatos patients from the Oak Meadow Drive location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective Oak Meadow Drive eye surgery and eye exams. Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. offer... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/oak-meadow-drive/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/oak-meadow-drive/">Oak Meadow Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. is proud to serve the eye care needs of their Los Gatos patients from the Oak Meadow Drive location of Spectrum Eye Physicians. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective Oak Meadow Drive eye surgery and eye exams. Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. offer the comprehensive eye care services that you have come to expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians. If you are in need of an eye exam or other vision care, the compassionate and professional staff at our Oak Meadow Drive office is here for you!</p>



<h2>Eye Care Services Provided at our Oak Meadow Drive Location</h2>



<h3>Conditions We Treat:</h3>



<ul><li>blepharitis (inflammation of the eyelids)</li><li>cataracts</li><li>complications with contact lens wear</li><li>corneal disease</li><li>diabetic exams</li><li>pink eye (infectious conjunctivitis)</li><li>macular degeneration</li><li>glaucoma</li><li>flashes &amp; floaters</li><li>eyelid cancers</li><li>dry eyes</li><li>tearing (epiphora)</li><li>retinal tear</li><li>retinal detachment (evaluation)</li><li>watery, itchy eyes (allergic conjunctivitis)</li><li>retinopathy</li></ul>



<p><strong>In addition to treating the conditions listed above, Dr. Ryan Basham, M.D. also provides:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Annual eye exams</li><li>Emergency eye exams</li><li>Dilated eye exams</li><li>Refraction</li></ul>



<p><strong>Surgical Treatment Including:</strong></p>



<ul><li>Cataract surgery (including laser-assisted with the LenSx femotsecond laser) with the full spectrum of lens implants (e.g. monofocal, toric, ReSTOR(r) / Technis(r) multifocal)</li><li>Ocular surface surgeries (e.g. pterygium, conjunctival tumors)</li><li>Glaucoma treatment with medical and laser eye surgery (e.g. laser trabeculoplasty, iridotomy, iridoplasty)</li><li>Anterior chamber reconstruction, and IOL repositioning (e.g. iris-fixated and scleral-fixated IOL&#8217;s)</li></ul>



<h3>Eye Care for the Entire Family</h3>



<p>While many eye conditions, such as cataracts and glaucoma, develop in older patients, the team at Spectrum Eye Physicians believes that it is important to start regular eye exams at an early age. We offer comprehensive services to all members of your family including full child vision care services. When children receive regular and routine eye care, beginning at a young age, they are more likely to continue healthy eye care habits throughout their lives. Vision issues can also be a factor in how your child performs at school, with poor eyesight causing many academic problems when left untreated.</p>



<p>It is also important for adults to receive regular eye care especially as they near middle age and their retirement years. Conditions such as macular degeneration, glaucoma, and cataracts can be asymptomatic during their early stages. Regular vision care can detect these conditions when they start thus increasing the patient&#8217;s chances of protecting their vision.</p>



<h3><br>Schedule an Appointment with Spectrum Eye Physicians at Oak Meadow Drive</h3>



<p>If you are in need of comprehensive eye care in the Los Gatos area, please give our Oak Meadow Drive office a call today at (408) 354-4740. We are conveniently located at 212 Oak Meadow Drive&nbsp;Los Gatos. We look forward to serving the eye care needs of your entire family very soon!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/oak-meadow-drive/">Oak Meadow Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Samaritan Drive</title>
		<link>/locations/samaritan-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/samaritan-drive/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Superior Eye Care by Qualified San Jose Eye Doctors Spectrum Eye Physicians&#160;provide&#160;superior eye care and the very best in a San Jose eye exam. At Spectrum Eye Physicians, your San Jose eye exam is conducted by well-trained and experienced&#160;eye doctors&#160;lead&#160;by excellent&#160;and compassionate doctors,&#160;Dr. James C. Liu,&#160;MD and&#160;Dr. Robert&#160;Mastman, MD. Meet Our Top San Jose Eye... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/samaritan-drive/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/samaritan-drive/">Samaritan Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2><strong>Superior Eye Care by Qualified San Jose Eye Doctors</strong></h2>



<p>Spectrum Eye Physicians&nbsp;provide&nbsp;superior eye care and the very best in a San Jose eye exam. At Spectrum Eye Physicians, your San Jose eye exam is conducted by well-trained and experienced&nbsp;eye doctors&nbsp;lead&nbsp;by excellent&nbsp;and compassionate doctors,&nbsp;Dr. James C. Liu,&nbsp;MD and&nbsp;Dr. Robert&nbsp;Mastman, MD.</p>



<h2><strong>Meet Our Top San Jose Eye Doctors at Spectrum Eye Physicians&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>Dr. James C. Liu earned his ophthalmology residency at LSU in New Orleans where he also completed a fellowship in laser vision corrective surgery. He mainly practices&nbsp;at our Samaritan Drive clinic where he&nbsp;is specialized in refractive surgery and is one of the early investigators of the use of the&nbsp;excimer&nbsp;laser for laser vision correction surgery. Dr. Liu also conducts&nbsp;eye surgery and is an expert in corneal problems, disease, and transplantation.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Dr. Robert&nbsp;Mastman, MD&nbsp;trained in Ophthalmology in Buffalo, New York and is a specialist in cataract, Ophthalmologic Plastic surgery, and corneal laser treatments. Dr.&nbsp;Mastman&nbsp;conducts eye surgery in our San Jose office and has performed thousands of&nbsp;eye surgeries&nbsp;including PPK (Photorefractive&nbsp;Keratectomy) and&nbsp;LASIK&nbsp;operations.</p>



<h2><strong>San Jose Eye Exam and Treatments of Eye Diseases&nbsp;</strong></h2>



<p>At Spectrum Eye Physicians our&nbsp;eye doctors&nbsp;perform a complete eye exam including a check of visual acuity, a slit lamp exam of the front of the eye, a dilated exam to examine the retina (back of the eye) and a refraction to determine if any corrective lenses are needed. Prescription eyeglasses and frames and contact lenses are available from the optical department which is staffed by licensed Doctor of Optometry. Eye diseases evaluated and treated include Glaucoma, Cataracts, Macular Degeneration, Dry Eyes, Pediatric Child Eye Health Exams, Ortho-K treatments and cosmetic eye surgery.</p>



<h3><strong>Contact Us Today</strong></h3>



<p>At our&nbsp;ophthalmology&nbsp;office,&nbsp;you will receive the very best in eye care by our San Jose eye doctors and the entire eye care team. Whether you need an eye exam or&nbsp;eye surgery for cataracts or a corneal disease, you can be assured of competent, compassionate treatment by experienced&nbsp;Board Certified San Jose eye doctors.&nbsp;</p>



<p>To make an appointment at&nbsp;Spectrum Eye Physicians – Samaritan Drive&nbsp;clinic, call&nbsp;(408) 358-2029 today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/samaritan-drive/">Samaritan Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Laser Center in San Jose</title>
		<link>/locations/laser-center-in-san-jose/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/laser-center-in-san-jose/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/laser-center-in-san-jose/">Laser Center in San Jose</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/laser-center-in-san-jose/">Laser Center in San Jose</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sunnyslope Drive</title>
		<link>/locations/sunnyslope-drive/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/sunnyslope-drive/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physicians at our&#160;Sunnyslope Drive location are proud to serve the eye care needs of their Hollister patients. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective eye surgery and eye exams. We offer the comprehensive eye care services that you have come to expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians.... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/sunnyslope-drive/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/sunnyslope-drive/">Sunnyslope Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The physicians at our&nbsp;Sunnyslope Drive location are proud to serve the eye care needs of their Hollister patients. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective eye surgery and eye exams. We offer the comprehensive eye care services that you have come to expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians. If you are in need of an eye exam or other vision care, the compassionate and professional staff at our Sunnyslope Driveoffice is here for you!<br></p>



<h2>Eye Care Services Provided at our Sunnyslope Drive Location</h2>



<p><br>Conditions We Treat:<br><br>* blepharitis (inflammation of the eyelids)<br>* cataracts<br>* complications with contact lens wear<br>* corneal disease<br>* diabetic exams<br>* pink eye (infectious conjunctivitis)<br>* macular degeneration<br>* glaucoma<br>* flashes &amp; floaters<br>* eyelid cancers<br>* dry eyes<br>* tearing (epiphora)<br>* retinal tear<br>* retinal detachment (evaluation)<br>* watery, itchy eyes (allergic conjunctivitis)<br>* retinopathy<br><br><br>In addition to treating the conditions listed above, our physicians also provide:<br><br><br>* Annual eye exams<br>* Emergency eye exams<br>* Dilated eye exams<br><br>* Refraction<br>Surgical Treatment Including:<br><br><br>* Cataract surgery (including laser-assisted with the LenSx femotsecond laser) with the full spectrum of lens implants (e.g. monofocal, toric, ReSTOR(r) / Technis(r) multifocal)<br>* Ocular surface surgeries (e.g. pterygium, conjunctival tumors)<br>* Glaucoma treatment with medical and laser eye surgery (e.g. laser trabeculoplasty, iridotomy, iridoplasty)<br>* Anterior chamber reconstruction, and IOL repositioning (e.g. iris-fixated and scleral-fixated IOL&#8217;s)<br></p>



<h2>Eye Care for the Entire Family</h2>



<p><br>While many eye conditions, such as cataracts and glaucoma, develop in older patients, the team at Spectrum Eye Physicians believes that it is important to start regular eye exams at an early age. We offer comprehensive services to all members of your family including full child vision care services. When children receive regular and routine eye care, beginning at a young age, they are more likely to continue healthy eye care habits throughout their lives. Vision issues can also be a factor in how your child performs at school, with poor eyesight causing many academic problems when left untreated.<br><br>It is also important for adults to receive regular eye care especially as they near middle age and their retirement years. Conditions such as macular degeneration, glaucoma, and cataracts can be asymptomatic during their early stages. Regular vision care can detect these conditions when they start thus increasing the patient&#8217;s chances of protecting their vision.<br></p>



<h3>Schedule an Appointment with Spectrum Eye Physicians at Sunnyslope Drive</h3>



<p>If you are in need of comprehensive eye care in the Hollister area, please give our Sunnyslope Drive office a call today at 831-637-0705. We are conveniently located at 930 Sunnyslope Drive Ste E-2 Hollister, CA 95023. We look forward to serving the eye care needs of your entire family very soon!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/sunnyslope-drive/">Sunnyslope Drive</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Green Valley Road</title>
		<link>/locations/green-valley-road/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[onur]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://spectrumeye.local:8888/locations/green-valley-road/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physicians at our Green Valley Road location are proud to serve the eye care needs of their Watsonville patients. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective eye surgery and eye exams. We offer the comprehensive eye care services that you have come to expect from Spectrum... <a class="moretag ui-read-more" href="/locations/green-valley-road/" title="Click Here to Read More">Read More</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/green-valley-road/">Green Valley Road</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The physicians at our Green Valley Road location are proud to serve the eye care needs of their Watsonville patients. This location is fully equipped with the advanced equipment necessary to provide safe and effective eye surgery and eye exams. We offer the comprehensive eye care services that you have come to expect from Spectrum Eye Physicians. If you are in need of an eye exam or other vision care, the compassionate and professional staff at our Green Valley Road office is here for you!</p>



<h2>Eye Care Services Provided at our Green Valley Road Location</h2>



<p>Conditions We Treat:</p>



<p>* blepharitis (inflammation of the eyelids)<br>* cataracts<br>* complications with contact lens wear<br>* corneal disease<br>* diabetic exams<br>* pink eye (infectious conjunctivitis)<br>* macular degeneration<br>* glaucoma<br>* flashes &amp; floaters<br>* eyelid cancers<br>* dry eyes<br>* tearing (epiphora)<br>* retinal tear<br>* retinal detachment (evaluation)<br>* watery, itchy eyes (allergic conjunctivitis)<br>* retinopathy</p>



<p>In addition to treating the conditions listed above, our physicians also provide:</p>



<p>* Annual eye exams<br>* Emergency eye exams<br>* Dilated eye exams</p>



<p>* Refraction<br>Surgical Treatment Including:</p>



<p>* Cataract surgery (including laser-assisted with the LenSx femotsecond laser) with the full spectrum of lens implants (e.g. monofocal, toric, ReSTOR(r) / Technis(r) multifocal)<br>* Ocular surface surgeries (e.g. pterygium, conjunctival tumors)<br>* Glaucoma treatment with medical and laser eye surgery (e.g. laser trabeculoplasty, iridotomy, iridoplasty)<br>* Anterior chamber reconstruction, and IOL repositioning (e.g. iris-fixated and scleral-fixated IOL&#8217;s)</p>



<h2>Eye Care for the Entire Family</h2>



<p>While many eye conditions, such as cataracts and glaucoma, develop in older patients, the team at Spectrum Eye Physicians believes that it is important to start regular eye exams at an early age. We offer comprehensive services to all members of your family including full child vision care services. When children receive regular and routine eye care, beginning at a young age, they are more likely to continue healthy eye care habits throughout their lives. Vision issues can also be a factor in how your child performs at school, with poor eyesight causing many academic problems when left untreated.</p>



<p>It is also important for adults to receive regular eye care especially as they near middle age and their retirement years. Conditions such as macular degeneration, glaucoma, and cataracts can be asymptomatic during their early stages. Regular vision care can detect these conditions when they start thus increasing the patient&#8217;s chances of protecting their vision.</p>



<h3>Schedule an Appointment with Spectrum Eye Physicians in Freedom</h3>



<p>If you are in need of comprehensive eye care in the Santa Cruz or Watsonville area, please give our Green Valley Road office a call today at (831) 728-2020. We are conveniently located at 160 Green Valley Road, Ste. 202, Freedom, CA 95019. We look forward to serving the eye care needs of your entire family very soon!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/locations/green-valley-road/">Green Valley Road</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Spectrum Eye Physicians</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
